http://www.qualitrol.com/help-support

Contact Us / Help & Support / Line Card
My Account
#1 GE Authorized PLC Support Center for Repairs, Parts, and Service | FREE GROUND SHIPPING FOR ALL ONLINE ORDERS
For Support & Answers Call 1-800-784-9385
Shop PartsWinmateRugged Mobile SolutionRugged Embedded ApplicationsRugged Industrial SystemRugged Industrial DisplayRugged Embedded ComputingVehicle Mounted ComputerDigital Signage and Bar TypeGE Fanuc - GE Intelligent PlatformsSeries 90-30 (IC693)Series 90-70 (IC697)Genius (IC660)RX7i (IC698)RX3i (IC694, IC695)QuickPanel (IC752, IC754)Series Six (IC600)Field Control (IC670)Series One (IC610, IC620)Series One Jr. (IC609)Series Three (IC630)Series Five (IC655)Series 90-20 (IC692)VersaMax (IC200)ManualsSoftwareHorner ElectricAllen-BradleySLC 500ControlLogixPLC-5PanelViewSiemensSimatic S7-300Simatic S7-400Simatic HMISimatic S7-200Siemens Simatic IPCEpsonProfaceProface HMIProface IPCProface Panel MonitorsSoftwareAccessoriesMOXAEthernet SwitchesProtocol GatewaysSecure RoutersSerial Device ServersSFP ModulesPoplinkPL SeriesPL Series KitBracket SeriesHDPL SeriesPanelsphere SeriesEnclosure SeriesHornerXL OCS SeriesMicro OCS SeriesRCC SeriesComputer DynamicsFlat Panel ComputersFlat Panel MonitorsIndustrial WorkstationsCCSBar LightsDome LightsFlood LightsRing LightsSquare LightsControllers Cables & AccessoriesMiscellaneous ControlsRepair PartsGE Fanuc PLC Factory Certified RepairAllen Bradley PanelView HMI RepairSiemens Simatic HMI RepairGE QuickPanel HMI RepairHMI Repairs / IPC RepairEPSON Robotics Factory Certified Repair & SupportGE Multilin RepairBreuer Ecovert Drive RepairProface RepairUticor RepairMaple Systems RepairEaton Cutler-Hammer PanelMate RepairXycom RepairRed Lion HMI RepairComputer Dynamics Industrial (CDI) RepairsTechnical SupportNews & BlogSell Surplus PartsEngineering Services
Customer EducationContact UsHelp & Support
Request a Quote
Contact Us
Home   /
Help Support Is your system down? Call us at 1-800-784-9385
Help & Support
Help & Support
At Qualitrol International, the up-time of your machines is our biggest concern. We have designed our business to meet that goal –
Quality 	parts on the shelf ready to ship today
3-5 day 	Repair turnaround
24/7 	Technical phone support
A team of 	GE-Trained Engineers available to come to your site as needed
Technical 	Resources and on-line Ordering capabilities available on our website any time, day or night.
Access to these services is just a phone call away - 1-800-784-9385
Below you will find information on Warranties and Returns, our Privacy Policy and our Terms & Conditions.
Warranties and Returns
All New 	PLC parts come with a one (1) year warranty.
All 	Recertified and Remaufactured PLC parts come with our exclusive two (2) year warranty.
All 	Repairs are covered with a two (2) year warranty.
In the 	event that your new or remanufactured part or your repaired part do 	not work to specifications when you receive them, simply send an 	email to products@qualitrol.com stating your name, email address, 	the part number of the failed part, when you bought it from us and 	the failure symptoms. We will promptly provide you with a Return 	Authorization. In the event of a down situation and based on stock 	availability, we may be able to provide a replacement immediately.
Privacy Policy
Qualitrol International is committed to protecting your privacy when visiting our web site. We recognize the need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information that you share with us on the Qualitrol.com website.
Collection of Personal Information
You may visit this site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. In order to receive proprietary information, to obtain access to certain features of our site or to request additional information from us, we may, however, request that you share personal information with us. If you choose to provide personal information (such as name, address, telephone number, fax number, or email address), we assure you that we will take appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of our web site, but you may be unable to access certain information, options, or services.
Information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected by Qualitrol International. This information may include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring web site addresses. This information is used by Qualitrol International to analyze trends and statistics, administer the site and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, when tracking these IP addresses, the individual user remains anonymous to Qualitrol International.
Qualitrol International does not install cookies or any other software on your computer.
Use of Personal Information
Qualitrol International will utilize your personal information to send you the information that you have requested from our site or to alert you to product upgrades or updated product information. From time to time, Qualitrol International may contact you via phone, email, or postal mail with information about various products and services. If you do not want to receive such communication, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of receiving further marketing information from Qualitrol International by contacting us via email at privacy@qualitrol.com or by clicking on the ‘Opt-Out’ link on the bottom of most emails.
In some cases, Qualitrol International may use a third-party, web-based email service when sending an email to many addresses at once. Only email addresses are passed to this service for tracking purposes; no other personal information is shared. Qualitrol International has a password-protected account with this provider so all information is secure and can be seen only by the employees of Qualitrol International who have password privileges to the account.
Qualitrol International will not sell, trade, or rent to any third party the information you provide through our website.
Changes to Policy
If Qualitrol International decides to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this page so you are always aware of what information we collect and how we will use it. We invite you to check this policy from time to time.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or comments about this Policy or would like further information, please contact us at privacy@qualitrol.com. We will address any issues to the best of our ability.
Qualitrol International3030 Whitehall Park Dr.Charlotte, NC 28273800-784-9385
Shop Parts
Sell Surplus Parts
Repair Your Parts
Technical Support & Resources
Why Choose Qualitrol?Terms & Conditions
News & Events
Help & Support
My Account
Contact UsRepair Line Card
Email Newsletter Sign-Up
Please check the captcha bellow, and click the checkmark to sign up.
© Qualitrol International 2020.   All Rights Reserved.
Sitemap  /  Terms & Conditions
New Account Required
If you had an account on the previous version of our site, please click here to create a new account.  Our new website contains enhanced security and account features that will require you to recreate your customer account. We apologize for any inconvenience.
Create Account
Close
